Ben: Can you believe it?I bagged an A-minus on the test.How'd you
do
卢克:这有什么.
Luke: No big deal.
本:A加?
Ben: A-plus?
卢克:不过猜对了几道题.
Luke: Made some lucky guesses.
本:猜代数?
Ben: In algebra?
卢克:数学不是什么精密科学.
Luke: It's not like math is an exact science.
卢克:好吧,下次我得个B.
Luke: Okay, I'll get a B next time.
本:那是萨莎索罗斯基.今天是萨莎要请我去参加赛迪霍金斯舞会的日子.
Ben: That's Sasha Soroski.Today's the day Sasha's going to ask me to the Sadie
Hawkins dance
卢克:你怎么知道的?
Luke: How do you know?
本:哦,这是我征服女人计划的结果.
Ben: Well, it's the payoff of my master plan of conquest.
卢克:你的什么?
Luke: Your what?
本:第一步:不理她;第二步:午饭时,
Ben: Phase one; I ignored her.
我坐在她对面决不看她一眼;
Phase two; sat across from her in the lunchroom, never made eye contact.
第三步:想方设法和她进同一个英语班,坐在她后面一年,
Phase three; pulled some strings to get into her English class.
不和她说一句话.
Sat behind her the whole year; never talked to her once.
卢克:整个学期,你就是这么做的?
Luke: You've been doing this all semester?
本:别傻了.我从六年级就开始了.
Ben: Don't be silly.Since sixth grade.
这样做很值得,
And it's definitely worth it, because now I've become that unattainable,
因为现在我成了她可望而不可及,求之不得的神秘人物.
desirable, man of mystery.
卢克:很好…
Luke: Okay...
本:她想死我了!
Ben: She wants me so bad!
卢克:什么!
Luke: What!
本:什么什么,你瞎了吗?她都用眼睛把我的衣服扒掉了.
Ben: What, are you blind?She practically undressed me with her eyes.
卢克:别臭美了.
Luke: That little tease.
本:我该把这可怜的姑娘从爱的饥渴中拯救出来
Ben: It's time to put that poor, love-starved girl out of her misery.
谢丽尔:嗨,本.
Cheryl: Hi, Ben.
本:嗨,谢丽尔.
Ben: Hi, Cheryl.
卢克:嘿,怎么了?
Luke: Hey, what's going on?
谢丽尔:真巧啊,又碰到你了.
Cheryl: What a coincidence running into you.
本:这是今天第18次巧合了.
Ben: This is the eighteenth coincidence today.
谢丽尔:这是因为我好像记住了你的行动安排.
Cheryl: Somehow I seem to have memorized your schedule.
卢克:真的?
Luke: You did?
本:听我说,谢丽尔,我们待会再聊好吗?我有点忙.
Ben: Look, uh, Cheryl, can we talk later?I'm kinda busy.
谢丽尔:那我们的历史作业怎么办?
Cheryl: Too busy for our history presentation?
本:我们的历史作业?
Ben: Our history presentation?
谢丽尔:上周在班上,我们结成学习对子了.
Cheryl: We signed up as partners in class last week.
本:我不记得啊.
Ben: I don't remember that.
谢丽尔:你当时在睡觉呢;我帮你举的手.那么,
Cheryl: You were sleeping; I held up your hand.
你想什么时候跟我一起做作业?放学后吗?
So, when do you want to get together to work on it?After school?
本:这不行.
Ben: Not really.
谢丽尔:今晚?
Cheryl: Tonight?
本:我们再说吧.
Ben: We'll discuss it.
谢丽尔:今天深夜?
Cheryl: Later tonight?
本:听着,谢丽尔,我和卢克有些男人之间的事要谈.
Ben: Look, uh, Cheryl, Luke and I have got some man things to talk about.
你知道,像吐痰啊,抓痒啊.
You know, spitting...scratching.
本:什么?
Ben: What?
谢丽尔:我还想问一句…周六晚上你能和我一起去赛迪霍金斯舞会和我跳舞吗?
Cheryl: I also wanted to know....
would you go to the Sadie Hawkins dance with me on Saturday night?
本:呃,我很愿意,但我妈妈有事.
Ben: Uh, gee, I'd like to, but my mom's come on.
谢丽尔:是也许?
Cheryl: Is that Maybe?
本:不,我不知道.那个晚上,我妈妈要做手术.
Ben: No, I don't know.I think that's the night my mom's having her surgery.
谢丽尔和卢克:真的?
Cheryl and Luke: Really?
谢丽尔:她怎么了?
Cheryl: What's wrong with her?
本:呃,没什么大事,她要,呃,捐一个肾.
Ben: Um, nothing serious; she's, uh, donating a kidney.
谢丽尔:哦,我的天啊.捐给谁?
Cheryl: Oh, my gosh.To who?
本:哦,谁需要就给谁.
Ben: Oh, whoever pops up.
谢丽尔:哇!她真慷慨.
Cheryl: Wow!She's really generous.Now I can see why you're so sweet.
怪不得你会这么可爱.那好吧,再见了.
Okay, then, we'll see.
本:是的,好的.
Ben: Yeah, right.
谢丽尔:拜!
Cheryl: Bye!
本:另外,萨莎还在等我呢.(向手掌吹气)这会要她命的.
Ben: Anyway, Sasha awaits.(blows in palm) Won't kill her.
本:好吧,我让你等的时间够长了.
Ben: All right, I've let you dangle long enough.
你梦寐以求的爱情就在这里.
Your hunk-a-hunk-a-burning love is here.
克莉丝:迈克回家了吗?我今天开始有家庭作业了.
Chrissy: Is Mike home yet?I got my first homework assignment today.
杰森:噢-哦,我觉得迈克不应该是你要找的人.
Jason: Oh-ho, I'm not so sure Mike's the one you want to ask for help.
克莉丝:他当然是;他可以告诉我怎么逃做作业.
Chrissy: Sure he is; he can tell me how to get out of it.
杰森:你为什么想逃作业呢?
Jason: Why do you want to get out of it?
克莉丝:爸爸,我们谈的不是到"后院去捡片叶子"这样简单的事.这太难了.我必须告诉全班,你们干什么工作.
Chrissy: Dad, we're not talking "bring in a leaf from the backyard."  This is big time; I have to tell my class what your jobs are
麦琪:哦,宝贝,这很意义.我们两个可以帮你的.
Maggie: Well, honey, that sounds like fun.And we'll both help you.
克莉丝:那么我必须要做吗?
Chrissy: So I'm stuck doing it?
开萝尔:猜一猜,
Carol: Guess who got an A on her first lab assignment from Felix "I flunked
谁第一做实验就从"六亲不认"的费利克斯手中得到一个"A".
my mother" Fitzsimmons.
麦琪:克莉丝,如果你要帮助的话,现在那个人来了.
Maggie: Chrissy, if you want help, there's the person to go to.
开萝尔:帮什么?
Carol: Help with what?
麦琪:克莉丝第一次留家庭作业了.
Maggie: Chrissy just got her first homework assignment.
开萝尔:哦!太好了!
Carol: Huh!That's wonderful!I remember mine.
我记得自己的第一次作业是要描述一年里自己最喜欢的季节.我选了冬天.
We had to describe our favorite time of year.I chose winter.
杰森:哦,对.那时我们还就此到学校参加了两次家长会.
Jason: Oh right, then we had to have two parent-teacher conferences over that one.
开萝尔:我至今难以相信,在那些5岁孩子里,
Carol: I still can't believe that I was the only five-year-old to see "
只有我把"雪人佛罗斯蒂"看作是死亡的象征.
Frosty the Snowman" as a metaphor for death.
克莉丝:我还是等迈克吧.
Chrissy: I'll wait for Mike.
本:莳萝条,花生酱,还有蛋黄酱.
Ben: Dill chips, peanut butter, and mayonnaise?
迈克:嘿,伙计们.
Mike: Hey, guys.
卢克:嘿,迈克,你想吃一块我做的神奇三明治吗?
Luke: Hey, Mike, you want one of my miracle sandwiches?
迈克:什么地方神奇?
Mike: What's the miracle?
本:你不咀嚼就咽下去的话.
Ben: If you can swallow it without hurling.
迈克:那就谢谢了.但是凯特今晚要为我做什么营养晚餐.
Mike: Thanks, anyway, but Kate's making a macrobiotic dinner for me tonight.
为了能咽下去,我一直什么都不吃,饿着呢.
I've got to be totally starved to choke it down.
嗨,伙计们,那儿有个女孩在那里走来走去的.
Hey, guys, there's a girl walking up the walk there.
她挺可爱的,和你的年龄差不多.她准是迷路了.
She's kind of cute; she's about your age.Must be lost.
本:哦,不,
Ben: Oh, no, it's Cheryl Murray.
那是谢丽尔默里.她老是缠着我做那愚蠢的历史作业.
We were supposed to work on that stupid assignment.What a pest!
真讨厌.你们给我找个借口.
Look, make an excuse for me.
迈克:本,我可没什么借口给你.
Mike: Ben, there is no excuse for you.
卢克:那你不做历史作业吗?
Luke: What about your history project?
本:只要还可以过疯狂的生活,我是不会做什么作业的.我要去跟"臭球"玩保龄去.
Ben: I'm not doing homework when I can be out living the wild life.I'm going bowling with Stinky.
卢克:你为什么不找个更好的事做呢?
Luke: Doesn't get any better than that.
迈克:嘿,你一定是谢丽尔吧.进来吧.呃,
Mike: Hi, you must be Cheryl.Come on in.
本必须得出去.呃,他说卢克会解释的.
Uh, Ben had to run out, uh, he, he said that Luke would explain.
卢克:呃,嘿,本必须到"臭蛋"家.事情很紧急.
Luke: Uh, hi.Ben had to go to Stinky's.It was an emergency.
谢丽尔:哦,事情很严重吗?
Cheryl: Oh, gee, anything serious?
卢克:不,老有紧急的事情在"臭蛋"身上发生.
Luke: Nah, emergencies happen a lot to guys named Stinky.
谢丽尔:你们没必要为他打掩护.因为我,
Cheryl: You don't have to cover for him.It's me, isn't it?
是吗?他以为我是个讨厌鬼.
He thinks I'm a dork.
卢克:哦,不,他没有.
Luke: Oh, no he doesn't.
谢丽尔:真的?
Cheryl: Really?
卢克:连想都没有.
Luke: He doesn't even think.
谢丽尔:哦,我想我要单独做作业了.
Cheryl: Well, I guess I'll work on my presentation alone.
卢克:哦,什么作业?
Luke: Well, what's it on?
谢丽尔:纪念哥伦布航行500周年.
Cheryl: The 500th anniversary of Columbus' voyage.
卢克:谢谢你提醒了我.知道吗,我得给他送个礼物.
Luke: Thanks for reminding me, you know, I still have to get him a gift.
谢丽尔:啊?
Cheryl: Huh?
卢克:是的,一个500岁的老探险家需要什么呢?
Luke: Yeah, what does a 500-year-old explorer need?
谢丽尔:人工呼吸?
Cheryl: Mouth-to-mouth?
卢克:想像一下吧,要是还活着,
Luke: Imagine how famous he'd be if he were alive today.
他该有多出名啊:上杂志封面;到白宫用午餐;
Cover of People Magazine.Doing lunch at the White House.
当好莱坞特邀嘉宾."我要送克里斯托夫哥伦布上船".
Guest shots on Hollywood Squares. "I'll take Christopher Columbus to block."
谢丽尔:或许他正在推销自己的香水:克里斯托夫哥伦布的重大发现:新大陆香水.
Cheryl: He'd probably be selling his own line of perfume;
Chris Columbus' Discovery: A New World Odor.
卢克:今日主题:发现新大陆的男人以及热爱他们的女人.
Luke: Today on Oprah: Men who exploit the New World,
and the women who love them.
谢丽尔:当然了他还要上阿赛尼奥的访谈节目.
Cheryl: And of course he'd be on Arsenio.
卢克:你可以这么写你的作业.
Luke: That's how you should do your project.
谢丽尔:是的,就像访谈节目.
Cheryl: Yeah, like a talk show.
卢克:女士们,先生们,
Luke: Ladies and gentlemen,
他证明了世界比匹兹堡士兵的屁股更圆,
he proved the world is bigger and rounder than the Pillsbury Doughboy's butt.
更大.下面有请克里斯托夫哥伦布!
Give it up for my man, Christopher Columbus!
谢丽尔和卢克:噢-噢-噢!
Cheryl and Luke: Woo-hoo-hoo!
卢克:哥伦布,三个字,新大陆.你怎么发现的?
Luke: Chris, two words.New.World.How did you do it?
谢丽尔:奉献,坚强,还有父母的定时体罚.
Cheryl: Dedication, perseverance, and regular floggings.
卢克:我懂了,好吧.你是位探险家,
Luke: I hear you.
女水手,航海家.还有什么?
Okay; you're an explorer, you're a sailor, you're a navigator.What next?
谢丽尔:我想指挥.
Cheryl: I want to direct.
卢克:休息一下;广告过后再回来.
Luke: We gotta take a break; we'll be right back.
谢丽尔和卢克:噢-噢-噢!
Cheryl and Luke: Woo-hoo-hoo!
克莉丝:本说,大家都到你办公室去,
Chrissy: So Ben says people come into your office,
然后躺在睡椅上.
and they lay down on the couch.
杰森:一些人是这样.是的.
Jason: Some people do, yes.
克莉丝:你让他们打盹吗?
Chrissy: Do you make them take a nap?
杰森:不,不,不,他们不睡觉.睡椅只是让他们放松.
Jason: No, no, no, they don't sleep.The couch just helps them relax.
克莉丝:你给他们洗脑是之前还是之后呢?
Chrissy: Is this before or after you shrink their heads?
杰森:不,这只是比喻.我只是跟他们谈话.
Jason: No, that's a figure of speech.I just talk to them.
克莉丝:谈什么?
Chrissy: About what?
杰森:谈他们想谈的一切事情,
Jason: Well, whatever they want to talk about.
以及需要谈的事情.
Whatever they need to talk about.
昨天有位女士来我这儿,
A lady came in to see me yesterday because she was really upset with her
因为她的丈夫惹的她非常生气.
husband.
克莉丝:像妈妈那样吗?
Chrissy: Like mommy?
杰森:不,不,这个女士总是生气.
Jason: No, no, this lady is upset all the time.
克莉丝:哦,像开萝尔.
Chrissy: Oh, like Carol.
杰森:不,让我解释一下,
Jason: No, no, let's see, um,
呃,人们认为是他们控制自己的行为.
people think they know the reasons they do things.
其实在每个人的内心都存在着第二个自己,正是他控制着我们的行动.
But inside of every person there's sort of a second person in there, and that's the real reason we do things.
每个人都有两个自己.这两个人一直互相打架,都企图控制第三个人.
They leaves 2 people, We'll always fight each other, try to control a third person
杰森:你如果懂得本我,自我和超我,就容易多了.
Jason: This would be easier if you understood the id, ego, and superego.
谢丽尔:你要是消防员就容易多了.
Cheryl: This would be easier if you were a fireman.
迈克:哦,天呐,
Mike: Oh, man, I am starved.
我饿死了.我要吃有肉有糖有肥油的东西.
I need something with meat or sugar or fat in it.
卢克:我以为你在凯特家吃过了.
Luke: I thought you ate at Kate's.
迈克:哦,是的,我想一想;哦,
Mike: Oh, well, we had, let's see; hay, stucco patties,
一小块馅饼,一小块蛋糕,还是一人一半.
and for dessert we split a Chia pet.
卢克:那我给你做块三明治怎么样?
Luke: Well how about I make you a sandwich with no ingredients that occur
肥的冒油的那种.
in nature?
迈克:哦,好的,这才是吃的东西.
Mike: Oh, all right, now that's food!
卢克:迈克,关于约会我想听听你的意见.本也想听.
Luke: Mike, I need your advice about dating.And Ben.
迈克:哦,这很简单,本并不合适你.
Mike: Well, that's easy enough; he's not your type.
卢克:我在谈谢丽尔呢.
Luke: I'm talking about Cheryl.
迈克:哦,就是之前来家里的那个女孩?
Mike: Oh, was that the girl who was here earlier?
卢克:是的,不过,她喜欢本.
Luke: Yeah.Anyway, she likes Ben.
迈克:哦,那她准是疯子.
Mike: Oh, so she's insane.
卢克:可能,但我喜欢她.我想,她也喜欢我.
Luke: Maybe, but I like her.And I think she likes me.
我是说,她人一走,我满脑子想的全是她.
I mean, ever since she left, she's all I can think about.
至于本,我觉得本是希望她马上消失.
And Ben; well, I get the impression he'd like her to disappear.
迈克:是吗?你怎么这么想呢?
Mike: Yeah? What makes you think that?
卢克:哦,他说过"我希望她消失"这样的话.
uke: Well, he said "I wish she'd disappear."
迈克:太好了!那还有什么问题啊?
Mike: Great!Then what's the problem?
卢克:我不知道约会的规则.
Luke: I don't know the rules about dating.
我再去见谢丽尔没什么吗?
Is it all right for me to see Cheryl again?
迈克:是的.听上去很不错.
Mike: Yeah, it sounds great to me.
你有了她,她有了你,本有了臭球.
I mean, you get her, she gets you, and Ben gets Stinky.
本:嗨,毛衣不错.
Ben: Hey, nice sweater.I got one just like it, only I never wear it.
我也有件这样的,可从来不穿.我穿上去像个傻瓜.
It makes me look like a dork.
卢克:其实这就是你的毛衣,我想你不介意吧.
Luke: Actually, this is your sweater.I mean, I didn't think you'd mind.
人人都说你穿着像个傻瓜.
Everybody says it makes you look like a dork.
本:嗨,她在那儿.
Ben: Hey, there she is.So, how's this sound?
你觉得这听起来怎么样?"呃,萨莎,
Uh, so Sasha, you doing anything special Saturday night between eight
你周六晚上8点到午夜有什么特别活动吗?"觉得怎么样?
and midnight?What do you think?
卢克:你低声下气又不失风度,刚刚好.
Luke: Nice balance between subtlety and begging.
本:哦,不,这不是谢丽尔嘛,至少我认为是她.
Ben: Oh, no, not now.It's Cheryl.At least I think it's Cheryl.
她看上去真漂亮.我说,你帮我个忙,
She looks so girl-like.Look, do me a favor.
别让她闲着,省得坏了我和萨莎的好事儿.
Keep her busy so she doesn't blow my chances with Sasha.
卢克:我得去上课了…
Luke: I gotta go to class...
谢丽尔:嘿,本,嘿,卢克.
Cheryl: Hi Ben, Hi Luke.
本:啊,呃,谢丽尔,哦,
Ben: Ah, uh, Cheryl, um, I gotta run.
我要跑了.卢克刚才问我一天的安排.也许你可以告诉他,是吗?
Luke was just asking me about my schedule.Maybe you could fill him in?
本:嘿,萨莎,说起赛蒂霍金斯的舞会…
Ben: Hi, Sasha.And speaking of the Sadie Hawkins dance...
本:我和你吗?什么,
Sasha: Me and you?What, are you joking?Not in a million years!
开玩笑吧?100万年以后也不行!别再跟我说话.
Don't ever speak to me again.
本:嘿,我已经有人约我去跳舞了.
Ben: Hey, I already have a date for the dance,
你就别在纠缠我了.我们结束了,宝贝.
so quit throwing yourself at me.It's over, baby!
本:哦,谢丽尔,我带来个好消息.
Ben: So, Cheryl, I've got some good news.
谢丽尔:用你妈妈肾的那个人找到了吗?
Cheryl: Have you found someone for your mom's kidney?
本:不,呃,实际上,没人需要.他们又送回来了.
Ben: No, uh, actually nobody needed it, so they put it back.
谢丽尔:噢-哈.
Cheryl: Uh-huh.
本:那么,呃,现在我可以跟你一起去跳舞了.
Ben: So, uh, now I can go to the dance with you.
谢丽尔:嘿,本,
Cheryl: Gee, Ben, I'm sorry, but since you didn't give me an answer,
很抱歉.因为你一直没有回信,我要和卢克一起去.
I'm going with Luke.
麦琪:好吧,来吧克莉丝,了解我工作的最好的防护上就是帮我干.瞧,我正在给报纸写一篇文章.
Maggie: Okay, c'mon Chrissy, the best way to learn about my job is to help me do it.Now, I'm writing an article for the newspaper.
克莉丝:是和谋杀有关的吗?
Chrissy: About murders and stuff?
麦琪:不,但这是非常重要的.
Maggie: No, but it's very important.
克莉丝:关于什么的?
Chrissy: About what?
麦琪:平头短裤.
Maggie: Boxer shorts.
克莉丝:不,是真的.(笑)
Chrissy: No, really.(laughing)
麦琪:宝贝,消费者调查报告是对不同产品进行测试,
Maggie:Honey, a consumer reporter tests different products to tell people
告诉人们该买哪一种.今天是测试男式平头短裤-
which ones they should buy. Today it's men's boxer shorts.
"快乐男士"平头短裤."如果短裤内的东西确实很重要,只有'快乐男士'牌短裤呵心保护".
Happy Man" boxer shorts. "If what's inside your shorts really matters,
"哦,好了,让我们测试一下腰带吧.
only Happy Man shorts will do." Uh, okay, let's test the waistband.
克莉丝:哎吆!
Chrissy: Ouch!
麦琪:哦,弹性必须很强.谁会愿意短裤滑到脚背上呢?
Maggie: Well, the elastic has to be strong.Who wants their shorts around their ankles?
克莉丝:我不愿意!
Chrissy: Not me!
麦琪:他们还声称该产品有特殊的防污能力.
Maggie: They also claim to be specially treated to resist stains.
我们来看看.
Well, we shall see.
克莉丝:哦,这可比爸爸的工作有趣多了.
Chrissy: This is a lot more fun than daddy's job.
麦琪:好了,我们呆会儿再干.先把饭从烤箱里拿出来.
Maggie: Okay, we'll finish up later.Let's get dinner out of the oven.
本:卢克呢?
Ben: Where's Luke?
麦琪:哦,我想他在…
Maggie: Well, I think he's...
本:(叫喊)卢克!
Ben: (yelling) Luke!
麦琪:…在楼上.
Maggie: ...upstairs.
本:(叫喊)卢克!
Ben: (yelling) Luke!
卢克:好嗓子!5英里之内的所有卢克都赶过来了.
Luke: Good pipes!Every Luke within five miles is on his way over.
本:真不敢相信你竟然当着整个学校的面羞辱我!
Ben: I can't believe you humiliated me in front of the entire school.
卢克:什么?
Luke: What?
本:你本来知道谢丽尔默里是我的地盘.
Ben: You knew Cheryl Murray was my territory.
卢克:你的地盘?你对她正眼都不瞧.
Luke: Your territory?You treat her like dog dirt.
本:我们的关系是特殊的.这跟你没关系.
Ben: We've got a special relationship.And it's none of your business.
卢克:哦,是吗?
Luke: Oh, yeah?Well, I'm making it my business.
可她跟我有关系了.我就要带她参加赛蒂霍金斯的舞会.
I'm the guy who's taking her to the Sadie Hawkins dance.
本:是吗?除非我死了!
Ben: Yeah?Over my dead body!
卢克:哦,这是可以办到的.
Luke: Oh that can be arranged.
本:真的?
Ben: Yeah?
卢克:真的!
Luke: Yeah!
麦琪:准备好吃晚饭了吗?
Maggie: Anybody ready for some dinner?
本:噢-噢.
Ben: Yum-yum.
卢克:咳,你.
Luke: Mm-boy.
本:这是我的椅子.
Ben: This is my chair.
卢克:不,不是你的.
Luke: No, it's not.
本:是,就是.我一直坐这里.离开萝尔最远的.
Ben: Yes, it is.I always sit here; the one furthest from Carol.
杰森:过来,本,你挨着你姐姐坐.
Jason: C'mon Ben, you sit next to your sister.
本:太感谢了.
Ben: Thanks a lot.
开萝尔:太感谢了.
Carol: Thanks a lot.
麦琪:好了,今晚应大家的特殊要求,吃小鸡炖蘑菇.
Maggie: Okay, tonight by special request; chicken and mushrooms.
本:谁的要求?我讨厌蘑菇1
Ben: Whose request?I hate mushrooms!
卢克:太谢谢您了,西沃太太.我最爱吃了.
Luke: Thanks a lot, Mrs.Seaver.You know it's my favorite.
本:我从不喜欢蘑菇.我早就说清楚了.我从不吃菌类食品.
Ben: I've never liked mushrooms.All my life I've made that very clear.I will not eat fungus.
克莉丝:哦!我也不吃!什么是菌类?
Chrissy: Eww!Me either!What's fungus?
本:就像卢克脚趾里的脏东西.
Ben: It's like the stuff between Luke's toes.
克莉丝:哦!
Chrissy: Eww!
卢克:就像你耳朵里的东西.
Luke: Like the stuff between your ears.
克莉丝:哦!
Chrissy: Eww!
杰森:本,怎么了你,
Jason: Ben, c'mon, watch it; your mother went to a lot of trouble....
看看,你妈妈费了这么大的劲…把鸡肉解冻…还得打开盛蘑菇汤的罐头.
defrosting...that chicken.And opening that can of mushroom soup.
本:我没说过我讨厌蘑菇吗?
Ben: Did I mention I hate mushrooms?
开萝尔:多大的事啊?把蘑菇挑出来得了.
Carol: What's the big deal?Just pick them out.
本:哦,如果要挑什么东西的话,
Ben: Well, if I was gonna pick something out,
我就挑一个新家,住在没有蘑菇的地方.
I'd pick out a new family who lived in a mushroom-free zone.
杰森:我们是不是在这里谈点儿令人愉快的话题呢?
Jason: Can we just have some pleasant conversation around here?
本:好.
Ben: Fine.
杰森:很好.卢克,你在学校交了很多新朋友吧!
Jason: All right.So Luke, you making a lot of new friends at school?
本:(呛着了)
Ben: (choking)
麦琪:本,你没什么吧?
Maggie: Ben, are you all right?
克莉丝:都是蘑菇弄的.
Chrissy: It's the fungus.
本:我很好.对不起,我差点噎死,把你们的食欲都破坏了.
Ben: I'm fine.Sorry if my near-death experience ruined anyone's meal.
卢克:没破坏我的.
Luke: Didn't ruin mine.
开萝尔:我很好.
Carol: I'm fine.
迈克:我也没问题.
Mike: No problem here.
本:开萝尔,请让卢克把盐递过来.
Ben: Carol, will you please ask Luke to pass the salt.
开萝尔:卢克,请把盐递过来.
Carol: Luke, pass Ben the salt please.
本:告诉他,他要在我伤口上撒盐,
Ben: Tell him I'll save him some in case he wants to pour any of it
我会给他留一些的.
in my wounds.
卢克:听着,我不明白你干嘛这么生我的气.
Luke: Listen, I don't know why you're so mad at me.
迈克说我什么也没做错.
Mike said I wasn't doing anything wrong.
本:迈克?你告诉他你怎么对我了?
Ben: Mike?You told him to do this to me?
迈克:本,你能安静会吗?我还想吃鸡呢.
Mike: Ben, would you keep it down?I'm trying to enjoy my chicken here.
本:哦.你这么喜欢吃饭?你可以吃我的.
Ben: Oh, you like dinner so much?You can have some of mine.
大家:(叫喊)嘿!你俩住嘴!
Entire family: (yelling) Hey!Stop it you two!
杰森: 你们几个怎么了?
Jason: What's going on between you guys?
迈克:你说你为什么要扔我?
Mike: What are you throwing food at me for?
本:对不起,抱歉.我不是故意扔你的.我是想扔他!
Ben: I'm sorry, excuse me.I didn't mean to throw food at Mike.I meant to throw it at him!
大家:(叫喊)别吵了!
Entire family: (yelling)
麦琪:我说了,住嘴!
Maggie: I said stop it!
杰森:出去,出去,
Jason: Get out of here!All you guys!
都出去.你也出去,迈克,
And you go with them, since you obviously have something to do with this,
很明显你准与这事有关.真没有想到.
Mike.Big surprise!
克莉丝:不能不走吗?我还从来没看过打食物仗呢.
Chrissy: Can't they stay?I've never seen a food fight before.
杰森:你乖乖的坐着,吃你的鸡和蘑菇.
Jason: You just stay here and eat your chicken and fungus.
迈克:算了吧,本,我们觉得你对谢丽尔并没有兴趣.
Mike: C'mon, Ben.We didn't think you were interested in Cheryl.
本:这并不意味着我想让这臭小子把她偷走!
Ben: That didn't mean I wanted her stolen away by some sniveling weasel.
卢克:是的,好吧,我这臭小子要教训你下.
Luke: Yeah, well, this sniveling weasel's gonna pop you one.
本:什么?
Ben: Yeah?
迈克:嘿,嘿,嘿,伙计们,伙计们,得了吧.你们为个姑娘打架,
Mike: Hey, hey, hey, guys, guys, c'mon.You're fighting over a girl.
好吧,为什么不省省为什么重要的事干一架呢?比如…谁掌握遥控器.
All right, now why don't you save it for the important stuff, like...who gets the remote control.
本:这事儿也算上;他为什么总是霸着遥控器.
Ben: That's another thing; how come he gets the remote control all the time?
卢克:什么?那在你的脸上换频道会怎么样?
Luke: Yeah?How would you like the channels changed on your face?
迈克:嘿,嘿,嘿,
Mike: Hey, hey, hey, guy, guys, knock it off.
伙计们,伙计们,别吵了.好吧,
All right now, Luke, c'mon,
卢克,你先上楼去,我跟本好好聊一会.
go upstairs and give me a minute to figure this out with Ben.
卢克:好的.我得去把自己耳朵里的土豆泥弄出来.
Luke: Sure, I gotta go Q-tip the mashed potatoes out of my ear.
迈克:好了,本,你介意告诉我发生什么事了吗?
Mike: Now, Ben, you mind telling me what's going on here?
本:谢丽尔爱慕我.她拜倒在神圣的本的脚下.
Ben: Cheryl adored me.She worshipped at the shrine o'Ben.
迈克:哦,行了.你觉得这公平吗,利用姑娘的崇拜来满足自己的虚荣心?
Mike: Oh, now, c'mon.Do you think that's really fair?To use some girl like that to stroke your own ego?
本:当然了.
Ben: Of course.
迈克:本,如果有个姑娘也这样对你呢?哦,很抱歉我这么说.我的头发没白吧?
Mike: Ben, what if some girl was doing the same thing to you?Oh, I'm sorry about that.How is my hair?
本:迈克,她让我感到自己很重要.
Ben: Mike, she made me feel important.
长期以来,
I mean, all my life I've been Seaver's little brother.
我都是西沃的小弟弟.大家都这么叫我.
I mean, that's all I ever heard.
我总算走出了你的阴影,现在却又和卢克搅在一起.
I'm finally out of your shadow, and now I'm the kid who lives with Luke.
我是说,他的成绩比我好,
I mean, he gets better grades than me, looks better in my clothes,
穿上我的衣服比我帅,我还要吃他喜欢的蘑菇.
and I choke on his mushrooms.
他甚至偷走了你该给我的建议.你是我哥哥,
He's even stealing the advice you should be giving me.
不是卢克的.
You're my brother, not Luke's!
克莉丝:嘿!
Chrissy: Hi!
杰森和麦琪:嘿,宝贝!
Jason and Maggie: Hi, Honey!
麦琪:课上的怎么样?你把我们的工作告诉他们了吗?
Maggie: How was school?Did you tell them about our jobs.
克莉丝:是的!太棒了!我还画了画呢.
Chrissy: Yeah!It was great.I even drew pictures.
杰森:哦,真不错.
Jason: Oh, how nice.
麦琪:你真有想像力.
Maggie: That's very imaginative.
克莉丝:对,太棒了.
Chrissy: Yeah, it was great.First I told them what daddy does.
我先说了爸爸的工作.我说,他把女人带进他的办公室,
I said he takes women into his office,
关上门,让她们躺在睡椅上.
closes the door and makes them lay on the couch.
一小时后,她们哭着出来,还给他钱.
An hour later they come out crying and give him money.
麦琪:那你是怎么说我的工作的?
Maggie: And what did you tell them about my job?
克莉丝:我说你的工作比爸爸有趣的多.你喜欢一遍又一遍地咬男人的平头短裤.因为我知道你喜欢"快乐男士"牌短裤.
Chrissy: I said that you have way more fun than daddy.I said that you
love to snap men's boxer shorts.Over and over.Cause you like a happy man
麦琪:哈-哈.
Maggie: Oh-oh.
克莉丝:我还说,结束后你往短裤上面倒热咖啡.
Chrissy: And I said when you finish, you pour hot coffee on them.
杰森:那么,你老师认为你的报告怎么样?
Jason: Well, what did your teacher think of this report?
克莉丝:她肯定很喜欢;她让我直接回家,
Chrissy: She must have liked it;
让你们给她打个电话.
she told me to go straight home and have you call her.
克莉丝:对,现在就给她打电话,好吗?(门铃声)
Jason: Yeah, why don't we do that right now.[Doorbell]
谢丽尔:嘿,本在家吗?
Cheryl: Hi, is Ben home?
杰森:是的,快进来.本!
Jason: Yeah, come on in.Ben!
本:谢丽尔,真是个惊喜.
Ben: Cheryl, what a pleasant surprise.
谢丽尔:我是来还你历史笔记本的,
Cheryl: I just came here to drop off your history notes,
因为我们不会在一起写作业了.
since we won't be doing our presentation together.
本:你在说什么呀?我们是学习对子啊.
Ben: What are you talking about?We're partners.
谢丽尔:不再是了.
Cheryl: Not anymore.
本:谢丽尔,我们的关系怎么了?
Ben: Cheryl, what happened to our relationship that let an outsider come
怎么让外人插进来呢?
between us?
谢丽尔:你从不打电话,从不约我,还在学校作弄我!
Cheryl: You never called, we never went out, and you made fun of me at school.
本:嘿,你不是在找茬吧.
Ben: Sure, if you want to nitpick.
不过,我们可以像过去一样相处.
But we can make things the way they used to be.
谢丽尔:像过去一样相处?
Cheryl: The way they used to be?
我在你的更衣箱前转悠,为你做作业,
Me hanging around your locker, doing your homework,
希望你能和我一起吃一顿午饭?
hoping that just once you'd eat lunch with me?
本:我没意见.
Ben: Worked for me.
谢丽尔:算了!这不会让你喜欢我的.
Cheryl: Forget it!It didn't make you like me.
知道吗?我对自己都不满意.
And you know, I didn't like me either.
就算卢克对我没兴趣,
Luke may not be interested in me,
事情也不会回到过去那个样子了.
but things are never going back to the way they were.
本:等等!,等一会儿,你是什么意思,卢克对你没兴趣?
Ben: Wait!Wait a minute.What do you mean; Luke's not interested in you?
谢丽尔:问他好了;他取消了约会.
Cheryl: Ask him; he broke our date.
本:是吗?为什么?
Ben: He did?Why?
谢丽尔:他说,因为什么家庭问题.
Cheryl: He said something about family problems.
本:听我说,谢丽尔,
Ben: Look, Cheryl, I've been a jerk and I'm sorry.
我是个傻瓜,我很抱歉.你愿意到厨房等我一会吗?
Would you mind going in the kitchen for a minute?
谢丽尔:为什么?你想让我给你做饭吗?
Cheryl: Why?Do you want me to fix you dinner?
本:就待一会,求你了.(喊)卢克!
Ben: Just for a minute, please.(yelling) Luke!
卢克:你喊什么?
Luke: You bellowed?
本:我说,你跟谢丽尔怎么了?
Ben: Listen.What happened between you and Cheryl?
卢克:没什么.没发生什么啊?
Luke: Nothing happened.Nothing's going to happen.
本:但我听你说过你真的喜欢她.
Ben: But I thought you said you really liked her.
卢克:是的,不过,
Luke: Yeah, but I didn't know you'd get so freaked.
我没想到,你会这么生气.而且,
And besides, you and your family have been so good to me,
你和全家对我这么好,我不能以怨报德.
this isn't how I wanted to repay you.
回头见.
See you around.
本:卢克,我们不需要你报答.我们希望你留在这儿.
Ben: Luke, we don't need you to repay us.You know, we want you here.
卢克:以前我领教过这种事.有一天,
Luke: I've seen it happen to kids before.
你做的太过分了,就成了不受欢迎的人.
One day you just go too far and wear out your welcome.
本:要是这样的话,开萝尔早就被赶出家门了.
Ben: If that were true, Carol'd have been gone a long time ago.
卢克:以前我们可从没为蘑菇和毛衣吵过架.
Luke: Well, we never did fight over mushrooms and sweaters before.
本:听我说,我决不和陌生人这样吵的.只有对惹我生气的兄弟,我才会这样.
Ben: Look, I'd never fight like that with a stranger.Only a brother...who really ticks me off.
卢克:我也是这样的.
Luke: The feeling's mutual.
本:好了,既然我们还得在一起相处下去,那你愿不愿意帮我个忙?
Ben: Well, since it looks like we're both gonna be here awhile, would you mind doing me a favor?
卢克:当然了.
Luke: Sure.
本:去看看我的"历史作业",就在厨房里.
Ben: Go check out my history presentation.It's in the kitchen.
卢克:你的历史作业?
Luke: Your history presentation?
本:快去吧,你嘴里一股蘑菇味.
Ben: Just get in there, mushroom-breath!
谢丽尔:卢克.
Cheryl: Luke.
卢克:谢丽尔.
Luke: Cheryl.
谢丽尔:听着,我…我还是走吧.
Cheryl: Listen, I...I'd better go.
卢克:不,不,不.你别走.我走.
Luke: No, no, no.You can stay; I'll go.
谢丽尔:不,不,不.你别走.
Cheryl: No, no, no.You can stay.
卢克:不,不,不.我走.
Luke: No, no, no.I'm going.
谢丽尔:卢克,你住在这里啊.
Cheryl: Luke, you live here.
卢克:哦.
Luke: Oh.
谢丽尔:那么,再见.
Cheryl: Well, see ya.
卢克:我说,谢丽尔.
Luke: Look, Cheryl.
我有两个解决方案.一是我可以三年之内不理你,直到你发疯地想我;
There's two ways I can play this; I can spend the next three years ignoring
you until you're crazed with desire for me
或者第二个方案-我这就邀请你参加赛蒂霍金斯舞会.
or plan B - I could ask you here and now to the Sadie Hawkins dance.
谢丽尔:不,你不能.应该是我邀请你.好吧,5个字:赛蒂霍金斯.
Cheryl: No, you can't.I'm supposed to ask you.Okay, two words.Sadie.Hawkins.
卢克:一个字:好.
谢丽尔和卢克:噢-噢-噢!
00:22:25,000
Luke: One word.Yes. Cheryl and Luke: Woo-hoo-hoo!